https://www.asymca.org/privacy-policy

CONTACT
PHONE HOTLINE:
(703) 455-3986
E-MAIL:
Contact
PHONE HOTLINE:
(703) 455-3986
E-MAIL:
info@asymca.org
PRIVACY POLICY
Privacy Policy
This website is operated by the Armed Services YMCA (ASYMCA). We recognize that many visitors to our site are concerned about the information they provide to us, and how we treat that information. We will not sell, share, or trade our donors’ names or personal information with any other entity, nor send mailings to our donors on behalf of other organizations. This policy applies to all information received by ASYMCA, both online and offline, including the ASYMCA website and mobile applications, as well as any electronic, written, or oral communications.
Learn more about policy by clicking the topics below.
Gathering and Use of Information
Our website automatically collects non-personally identifiable information on our site visitors. This information is used to compile statistics for our website such as the number of visitors to the site and which pages were viewed. If you ever have questions or would like to update your information you can reach us here.
Personally identifiable information is only collected when you voluntarily submit it, such as when making a donation. If you provide us with this information, we will use it to contact you and acknowledge your donation and as appropriate inform others of your kindness when donations are made in honor or memory of another. Other information collected is only used for its intended purpose such as processing a credit card donation or pay allotment from military active duty or retirement pay.
We do not sell, trade, or provide your name or contact information with any other organization or individual, except in those cases when a donor designates his or her contribution to a specific ASYMCA Branch. In these cases, we do provide contact information to the Executive Director of the designated ASYMCA Branch in order to acknowledge the donation. Executive Directors are told they may not use this information for any type of solicitation.
It is our policy to acknowledge the support of donors who contribute $1,000 or more by publishing only their names in our Annual Report. Requests to make a donation anonymously may be made on the appropriate contribution form and are always honored.
At certain points where personal information is collected on our site or through our direct mail campaigns, there may be a box where you may indicate you would like to be on a mailing list to receive information about other ASYMCA programs and services and about ways to support the ASYMCA. This election box only appears in places where personal information is collected.
A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. The ASYMCA uses non-identifying cookies to provide easier site navigation and access to forms. You can still use ASYMCA sites if your browser is set to reject cookies. Our cookies do not generate personal data, do not read personal data from your machine, and are never tied to anything that could be used to identify you.
ASYMCA’s Commitment to Online Security
Physical, electronic, and managerial procedures have been employed to safeguard the security and integrity of personal information. All ASYMCA employees with access to personal information obtained on ASYMCA websites or when you voluntarily submit information through a donation are bound to adhere to this policy as part of their employment with the ASYMCA.
We use PCI compliant systems to protect your financial information. We do not maintain any financial data in our systems. Our data systems are behind state of the art firewalls to ensure we protect your personal information.
Your Ideas
We encourage you to share your comments and questions with us. We promise to read all the mail you send to us, but we may not be able to respond to all of it. However, please note that we assume no responsibility for reviewing unsolicited ideas for our business (like product or advertising ideas) and will not incur any liability because of any similarities between your ideas and future ASYMCA products or programs. This means that we have no obligation to treat your idea submissions confidentially and that we can use them without paying you for them. Any and all idea submissions will be owned by ASYMCA exclusively and may be used by ASYMCA for any purpose, now or in the future. You can reach us here.
Links
ASYMCA’s website may contain “links” to other sites. We make every effort to only link to sites that share our high standards of decency, fairness, and integrity. We try our best to ensure that these links are safe for youth and appropriate for our users in general. However, since we cannot guarantee the content of every site to which we are linked, youth should always check with an adult before linking to any new sites.
Use of Materials on ASYMCA’s Website
Please remember that the trademarks, service marks, graphics, text, and other properties appearing within this website are the property of ASYMCA. Research information provided for downloading by visitors to our site may be used for personal or non-commercial use only. Otherwise, properties may not be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed without the prior written consent of ASYMCA. Except as expressly provided above, nothing contained herein shall be construed as conferring any license or right under any copyright or other intellectual property right.
CONNECT WITH US
National Headquarters
About
Our Services
COVID-19 Response
Locations
How to Help
Contact
©2020 Armed Services YMCA - 14040 Central Loop, Suite B, Woodbridge, VA 22193
Privacy Policy
The appearance of U.S. Department of Defense (DoD) visual information does not imply or constitute DoD endorsement.
